Previously on the show.
上集說到
The stars wanted to attract a crowd
星星們想藉
with the performance by the wolves and goats.
狼羊的表演吸引觀眾
But Wolffy was injured in an accident and couldn't perform.
可是灰太狼意外受傷無法表演
Elder Star had to take over Wolffy's role on stage.
長老星只能硬著頭皮頂替灰太狼上台
With the help of everyone,
最後在大家的努力下
the performance became wildly popular.
演出大受好評
What will happen next?
接下來會怎麼樣呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Amazing Power of the Stars"
《奇幻天空島之》
See? I said you can't get me, didn't I?
你看，我說抓不到我吧
Not necessarily.
那可說不定啊
We got you, Wolffy!
抓住你了，灰太狼！
This is awesome! Awesome!
太精彩了！太精彩！
Please come again next time!
歡迎下次再來
Switch on the lights.
開燈
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快樂
Oh, I'm sorry.
對不起
Thank you, everyone. I'm 800 years old.
謝謝大家！八百歲了
I finally have my powers.
終於有能力了
Wait... What powers do I have?
等等…我有什麼能力啊？
You're the only one who can discover your own powers.
你的能力只有你自己才能發現
Just like me.
就像我一樣
I tried for so long.
我試了好久好久
Until one day,
直到有一天
I found out that I would turn handsome when I'm alone.
我發現自己一個人的時候就會變帥
If you stay alone somewhere,
或許你找一個地方一個人待著
maybe you'll find out what your powers are.
就能發現你自己的能力
This is very worrying.
這麼麻煩
If only someone can tell me what my power is right away.
要是有人能夠直接告訴我就好了
Come here.
過來
Elder!
長老！
-Let me tell you... -Sure.
我告訴你…
That is...
就是…
the drama finale starring Flat-beak Allen, The Boy Who Loves Stars is airing soon.
扁嘴倫主演的《愛看星的少年》 就快結局了
Quick, go home and watch it!
快點回家看吧
Power!
能力！
Let me try again.
換一個吧
That's not right either. Let me try again.
也不是啊，再換一個
Power!
能力！
Uh! Sorry... Did I startle you?
對不起…我嚇到你了嗎？
Oh, your favorite toy car is broken.
原來是心愛的玩具車壞了
I wish it could move again.
我好想它能動起來
Let me see.
讓我看看
It's fixed! Thank you for making my wish come true.
車好了，謝謝你幫我實現了願望
Making a wish come true...
實現願望…
Could my power be making one's wish come true?
我的能力難道是實現願望？
Wouldn't that make me a wishing star then?
那我不就是願望星了？
My hair is tangled. The comb is stuck.
頭髮打結了，梳子拔不出來
Paddi, make a wish to Wishing Star Grandpa!
懶羊羊哥哥 你快向願望星爺爺許願吧
What? Wishing Star Grandpa?
願望星爺爺？
Hurry! What wish do you have?
快，你有什麼願望？
I just wish combs won't get stuck in my hair again.
我現在只希望梳子不再卡住我的頭髮
Let me handle it. Wish...
交給我吧，願望…
My wish came true...
真的實現了
I wish my television can be fixed!
我希望電視機能修好！
No problem!
沒問題！
Wish... come true!
願望…成真吧！
Wow! This is awesome!
哇！太厲害了！
I wish someone could sweep the floor for me.
我希望有人能代替我去掃地
You said Time Star...
你說時光星什麼…
This is great! Everyone's here to help me sweep the floor.
太好了，大家都來幫我掃地了
But I haven't used my power yet.
可是我還沒有施法呢
I was mistaken. I thought my wish came true.
原來搞錯了，還以為願望實現了呢
What wish?
什麼願望？
I can make all your wishes come true.
向我許願就能成真喔
All wishes will come true?
真的什麼願望都可以實現嗎？
Yes, they sure do.
是，是的
I wish...
我的願望是…
I'm not done wishing yet...
我剛才還沒許完願呢
Ahem! You guys.
你們…
Tibbie, come make a wish too.
美羊羊，妳也一起來許願吧
Village Chief!
村長！
-You should perform your own duty! -Right.
-自己的事情當然自己做 -對
We'll always remember Village Chief's teaching.
村長的教誨我們一直都記得
Who drank so much soda? It's ridiculous.
究竟是誰喝的汽水？這麼多
Why are you staring at me?
你們怎麼這麼看著我？
It really wasn't me this time.
這次真的不是我
Strangely though, these soda cans have not been opened yet.
不過奇怪的是 這些汽水好像都沒有開過呢
Regardless, it's wrong to litter here.
不管怎麼說 隨便扔在這裡也太沒有公德心了
What's going on?
怎麼搞的？
How come my soda bombs aren't exploding yet?
我的汽水炸彈怎麼還不爆？
Why didn't they explode?
為什麼不爆炸呢？
What's the problem?
究竟問題出在哪呢？
Wasn't this toy car broken?
這個玩具車，之前不是壞了嗎？
Wishing Star Grandpa fixed it for me.
是願望星爺爺幫我修好的
I invited him over too.
我還請他來玩了呢
Wishing Star Grandpa.
願望星爺爺
Dad, Wishing Star Grandpa is awesome.
爸爸，願望星爺爺可厲害了
He can make wishes come true.
他可以實現願望啊
-Really? Him? -Yes.
-他能實現願望？ -是的
Let me try then.
那我來試試吧
There's something wrong with my invention. I wish he could fix it.
我的發明出了問題
Sure thing.
交給我吧
Wish... come true!
願望…成真吧！
-It's done! -Really?
-好了！ -真的假的？
My wooden toy horse!
我的玩具木馬！
Dad, you're so mean!
爸爸好壞！
Son!
兒子！
Can you restore the wooden horse to its original state?
能把木馬恢復原狀嗎？
Sure, of course.
當然沒問題了
Then I'll leave that to you. Son!
那交給你了，兒子！
Wish… come true!
願望成真吧！
How come it didn't work?
怎麼沒反應啊？
One more time. Wish... come true!
再來一次，願望成真吧！
Did I overuse my power that it doesn't work?
難道之前用力過猛，能力失效了？
I have to fix it.
不修好可不行啊
I can't disappoint the kid.
不能讓孩子失望
My wooden horse!
我的木馬！
If he's able to make wishes come true,
既然他有實現願望的能力
I'll make him catch the goats.
那就用他來捉羊吧
Oh, right... Can you give this to Weslie for me?
對了，麻煩你幫我送給喜羊羊吧
Why?
為什麼啊？
Because it's his birthday today.
因為，今天是他的生日嘛
I see. Let me do it.
原來是這樣，交給我吧
Wait! Where're you going?
等等，你這是要去哪？
Didn't you tell me to deliver the present for you?
你不是叫我幫你送禮嗎？
Since you can make wishes come true,
既然你能實現願望
can't you deliver it to him right away?
不是一下子就能送到嗎？
Oh, sure... What's that?
那是當然了，那是什麼？
What?
什麼？
There's nothing there.
什麼都沒有啊
Where is the present?
禮物呢？
I've already delivered it to him for you.
已經幫你送過去了
Well done. Let me see if they like the gift.
好樣的 我去看看他們收到禮物開不開心
Oh, no! I have to deliver it now.
不好，我得趕快送過去
Good, I got here before Wolffy.
總算，在灰太狼之前到了
Grandpa Star?
星星爺爺？
Oh, Weslie, it's great you're here. Happy birthday.
喜羊羊，你來得正好，生日快樂
Thank you for your present.
謝謝您的禮物
Open it now.
快拆來看看
-Don't drop it. -Thank you.
-拿好 -謝謝
But how did you know it's my birthday today?
不過，你怎麼知道今天是我生日？
I didn't.
我不知道啊
-This is from Wolffy. -Wolffy?
-這是灰太狼送的 -灰太狼？
I've delivered the present. Goodbye.
我確實送到了啊，再見
It's a bomb!
是炸彈！
It should be about time.
時間應該差不多了
Why does this soda can look so familiar?
這汽水瓶怎麼這麼眼熟？
Why is it me again?
為什麼又是我？
Wolffy, I made your wish come true.
灰太郎，我幫你實現願望了
I know. Thank you.
我知道，謝謝你啊
Why are you hurt?
你怎麼傷成這樣？
Don't ask. I need some medicine now.
別問了，我現在需要藥膏
What?
怎麼了嗎？
No... It's nothing. Let me try again.
沒…沒什麼，我再試試吧
Hurry and make my wish come true.
那就請你快點實現我的願望吧
Wish...
願望…
What now?
又怎麼了？
Wow! It worked. My power is back.
成功了，我的能力又回來了
I need to go and help more people.
我要去幫更多的人
No. I should've just wished to recover.
不對啊 我直接許願恢復不就好了嗎？
Hey! Come back!
回來！
Hair Growth Star, do you have a wish?
長毛星，你有沒有想實現的願望啊？
Of course! I want to be handsome.
當然有了，我想變帥
No problem!
沒問題！
Wish… come true!
願望…成真吧
This is strange.
奇怪
Go try over there. Don't bother me when I'm having dinner.
你去那邊試吧，別打擾我吃飯
Do you have a wish?
你有沒有什麼心願啊？
-I would like to grow tall. -Wish… come true!
我想長高
I knew I have the power in me.
我就知道我有能力的
I just stood up. My wish didn't come true.
我只是站起來而已，願望沒實現啊
Why is my power so unsteady?
為什麼我的能力這麼不穩定呢？
What's going on?
怎麼了？
I finally found out that my power is to make wishes come true.
我好不容易才發現自己的能力 是實現願望
But my power is unsteady.
可是這能力老是不穩定
Are you sure your power is making wishes come true?
你確定你的能力就是實現願望？
It is. If you don't believe me, ask Wolffy.
真的，不信，你去問灰太狼
I found you!
找到你了！
I have one more wish. I would like to...
我還有一個願望，我想…
Are you all right? You're here just in time.
你沒事吧？你來得正好
-Are you all right? -Why did you shock me?
-你怎麼了？ -你幹麼電我？
Shock... That's impossible.
電…不可能啊
I can release electricity too?
我還能放電？
I have the power to make wishes come true and release electricity.
我竟然有實現願望的能力
You're thinking too much. Every star only has one power.
你想多了，每個星星只能有一種能力
But I made wishes come true for people earlier.
可是我之前的確實現了別人的願望啊
I helped repair Willie's toy car.
我之前幫助小灰灰修理好玩具車
I fixed Paddi's television.
又修好了懶羊羊的電視機
I also fixed Wolffy's invention.
還修好了灰太狼的發明
I must be a Wishing Star.
我一定是願望星啊
How about the rest? Did all the wishes come true?
除了這些呢，其它的願望都實現了？
I couldn't fix Willie's wooden horse.
我沒辦法修好小灰灰的木馬
I also couldn't deliver the present for Wolffy.
也沒辦法幫灰太狼送禮物
I couldn't make others grow handsome or taller.
還有不能讓人變帥和長高
You were conducting electricity and repaired the appliance by chance.
你帶電才碰巧修好電子產品
Therefore, you are Electric Star.
所以你是電流星
So I can't make wishes come true.
原來我沒法實現願望啊
My power seems quite useless.
我的能力好像沒什麼用呢
That's not true. It's a very useful power.
怎麼會呢？很有用啊
Awesome!
好厲害啊！
If you buy a ticket and come inside, it'll be even more amazing.
買票進去還有更精彩的喔
-I will buy a ticket. -Me too.
-我買 -我也買…
We sold more tickets today than yesterday. Your power is amazing.
今天比昨天多賣了很多票 你的能力太棒了
TO BE CONTINUED
（未完待續）